Guide to the Yale University Films Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Films and clips produced by University Public Information, circa 1978; Accession 1990-A-068
  - William Franklin and Stamp Act, undated (Box 20, Folder 729)
  - British-American, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 730)
  - Loyalists: Chronology, undated (Box 20, Folder 731)
  - Loyalists: Rough Draft, undated (Box 20, Folder 732)
  - Haiti, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 733)
  - Tufts World Peace Curriculum, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 734)
  - "Stalin", 1983-1987 (Box 20, Folder 735)
  - "Evolution of Western Law", 1985 (Box 20, Folder 736)
  - Enewetak, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 737)
  - Evolution of American Law, 1987-1988 (Box 20, Folder 738)
  - Bulletins from Bill P., 1985-1987 (Box 20, Folder 740)
  - Filmed Lectures, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 741)
  - Computer Tidbits, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 742)
  - Norick, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 743)
  - Pacific, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 744)
  - Yale University Films Correspondence, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 745)
  - Yale University Films-RWS, 1986-1988 (Box 20, Folder 746)
  - Equipment Warranty Regulations, Product Correspondence/ Instructions, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 747)
  - RWS Correspondence, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 748)
  - Tanzania, 1986-1987 (Box 21, Folder 750)
  - Bulletins from Diana, 1985-1988 (Box 21, Folder 751)
  - Publicity, 1986-1987 (Box 21, Folder 752)
  - RWS Loyalists, undated (Box 21, Folder 753)
  - Revised Draft RWS Loyalists, undated (Box 21, Folder 754)
  - Boswell for Defence: Marketing and Distribution, 1982-1985 (Box 21, Folder 755)
  - BoswellPublicity, 1985-1986 (Box 21, Folder 756)
  - LondonJournal, 1982-1984 (Box 21, Folder 757)
  - Boswell for the Defenceand London Journal: Mark Harris Correspondence, 1982-1986 (Box 21, Folder 758)
  - Boswell: Contracts, 1979-1983 (Box 21, Folder 759)
  - Boswell for the Defenceand London Journal: National Endowment for the Humanities Correspondence and Reviews, 1980-1984 (Box 21, Folder 760)
  - BoswellCumulative Analysis and Budgets, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 761)
  - John Stringer Correspondence, 1980-1982 (Box 21, Folder 762)
  - BBC/McGraw Hill/Heinemann Correspondence:Boswell, 1981-1983 (Box 21, Folder 763)
  - Ancillary Materials Information, 1983-1986 (Box 21, Folder 764)
  - Endowment, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 765)
  - Contractual Rights and Obligations: All Projects, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 766)
  - Evaluation Information, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 767)
  - Mission Statement Xeroxes, Endorsements of Yale University Films, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 768)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities Challenge Grant, 1983-1984 (Box 21, Folder 769)
  - Project Lists: Chronological, 1983-1986 (Box 21, Folder 770)
  - Transition: Media Design Studio, 1982-1985 (Box 21, Folder 771)
  - Minority Personnel: Vitas, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 772)
  - Mailing Service Information, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 773)
  - Executive Committee, 1983-986 (Box 21, Folder 774)
  - Boswell/Frontline Mailing Labels, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 775)
  - Information on Screening Rooms, undated (Box 21, Folder 776)
  - Copyright Forms, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 777)
  - Writers, Directors, 1984-1986 (Box 21, Folder 778)
  - Financial Sketches and Other Financial Matters, 1981-1985 (Box 21, Folder 779)
  - Funding Information: Foundations and Corporations, 1983-1984 (Box 21, Folder 780)
  - National Science Foundation, 1984-1985 (Box 21, Folder 781)
  - Film Festivals, 1985-1986 (Box 21, Folder 782)
  - ConnecticutPublic Television, 1984-1985 (Box 21, Folder 783)
  - WGBH, 1984-1985 (Box 21, Folder 784)
  - National Endowment for the Arts, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 785)
  - Public Broadcasting System Information, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 786)
  - "A More Perfect Union" Correspondence, 1983-1986 (Box 21, Folder 787)
  - Loyalists, 1984-1986 (Box 21, Folder 788)
  - Connecticut Public Broadcasting, 1984-1986 (Box 21, Folder 789)
  - Program on Art in Film: W. Stein, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 790)
  - Boswell: Supplement Requests, 1984-1986 (Box 21, Folder 791)
  - Boswell Papers, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 792)
  - A Class Divided, 1 (Box 22)
  - Boswell's London Journal, 2 (Box 22)
  - Boswell for the Defence, 2 (Box 22)
  - Piaget on Piaget, 1 (Box 22)
  - Stranger in the Family, 1 (Box 22)
  - Black Folklore
  - Give My Poor Heart Ease: Mississippi Delta Bluesmen, 1 (Box 22)
  - Two Black Churches, 1 (Box 22)
  - I Ain't Lying: Folktales from Mississippi, 1 (Box 22)
  - Made in Mississippi: Black Folk Arts and Crafts, 1 (Box 22)
  - The Ressurrectionists, 1 (Box 22)
  - The Making of "Butch Cassidy and the Sundance Kid", 1 (Box 22)
  - The Making of "Slaughterhouse 5", 1 (Box 22)
  - "Resurrectionist"
    - Sound reels, 20 (Box 23)
    - Outtakes, 4 (Box 23)
    - Photographic slides and negative (35mm) (Box 23)
  - "Olmstead"
    - Scripts, letters, catalogs, notes (Box 24–26)
  - Audiorecordings
    - Arthur Penn's class, Yale Film School, 1971 November 11, undated; 2 (Box 27)
    - Penn interview, undated; 2 (Box 27)
    - Weaver, A. Penn, 1971 January 21, undated; 6 (Box 27)
    - Hubley class, presentation of rough story board, 1973 March 13; 3 (Box 27)
    - Garland/Garvin, 2 (Box 27)
    - Roemer, 2 (Box 27)
    - Lerner's class, 2 (Box 27)
    - TV studio, 1 (Box 27)
    - Cockaboody, sound effects, 1 (Box 27)
    - Weaver, 9 (Box 27)
  - Adverstising layouts (Box 28)
- Yale University-produced films, Accession 2000-A-035
  The materials are open for research.
  - "The Resurrectionist", film reel (16mm) (Box 1)
  - "Ambrose Pare, Military Surgeon", film reel (16mm) (Box 2)
- "Piaget on Piaget", Accession 2002-A-133; videotape (VHS)
  - "Piaget on Piaget", videotape (VHS); Duration 42 minutes, 8 seconeds; Content appears to be from previous film to tape transfer. (Box 1)
- Advertising records from the Media Design Studio, circa 1982; Accession 2003-A-068
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2018.
  - Advertising records from the Media Design Studio, circa 1982 (Box 1)